Hello friends, welcome to our new
video and you are watching your own
YouTube channel Banking Jobs Guide which has all about
Banking Jobs.  Friends, if
you have the qualifications of graduation pass out,
whether
in any discipline, be it engineering or non-
engineering, if you have
obtained education qualification and you are also
waiting for apprenticeship vacancy
and especially for those candidates who are
willing to do apprenticeship in banking sector, then
for those candidates I have
brought a good vacancy here in which the
candidates can start filling their application form from today.
Friends, in this
you do
not have to make any application or payment nor do
you need to do any extra formalities.  There
is a simple form,
by filling it up you can participate in this opportunity.
Yes friends, let us
talk about ICICI Lombard General
Insurance, which everyone must be knowing about ICICI Bank.  There
is a unit of that.
Through this, an apprenticeship program was launched for graduate pass out candidates
for 2025-26.  So
application forms were sought from eligible candidates.  Friends,
for all its information, you will first have to
go to bfsi.com,
its official website.  You will get
to see all the details on this.  Here,
as you come to Career Opportunities,
you are given apprenticeship
opportunities.  Within this you will find
ICICI LBR General Insurance
Company Limited.  Above this you have to
click here.  As soon as you click on it,
a new page opens here.
ICICI LBA General Insurance Company Limited
Apprenticeship Programme Financial Year
First of all, here you are
given the link to fill the application form.
As soon as you click on it, a new
page will open here in which it is given
ICICI LBAD General Insurance Company Limited
Apprenticeship Program 2025 26. You have to
fill up your name on the basis of your details in your 10th marksheet.
You have to enter a valid email ID here
because all the correspondence will be done
through this email.  Valid
mobile number has to be entered.  Have to enter gender.
Date of birth has to be entered on the basis of 10th SSC mark sheet.
Categories
Locations Streams Which one do you have?
You have to enter your work experience here.  There is
arts, commerce,
management, science and technology.
So all types of streams are
asked for here.  You have to enter experience,
CTC, highest qualification.
You have to enter the date of highest qualification and submit it here.  As soon as
you submit, your application form will be
submitted from here and you will become eligible to
participate in this opportunity.
So friends, this is the
link to fill its application form.
Now there is a vacancy in it.  So,
as soon as you click on the job description here, there is a
small notice given here in
which the job description
is written.  Given you will gain exposure and
work in the following fields.  So here
you will be given apprenticeship in the following fields.  There will be
MIS
management, back office, compliance
management.  You will be given apprenticeship training within these three.   In which
you will be given real work experience.
Practically you will be
told how that
work is done in the general instant sector.  These
things will be very useful to you in the future.
It is possible that the company may give you
some opportunity in the future, if there are vacancies
then you can get some good opportunity here
too.
Friends, whatever information was available, I have
told you here.  Now if you
want to fill your application form, you can
go to its official website and submit your application
form.  So, there is
no information given here about the total number of vacancies.  The
last date for filling the application form is
also not shown here but the
application form has already started being filled.
So it is ongoing, now you can
easily submit your party's application form in it.
So friends, if you liked this much
video then like and
share it and if you have not joined the channel then
join the channel also because
you keep getting such new updates on this channel.  That's all for
this video, thank you.